Todd Nordquist

Alburquerque, NM

+1 (505) 206 - 0811

toddnordquist144@gmail.com Linkedin.com/in/todd-nordquist https://github.com/tnordquist

SUMMARY

I am a self driven software developer who wishes to be a valued member of a programming development team. My use of computer software and experience creating a website while in managerial positions for the past six years increased my passion for computer programming and development.

TECH SKILLS

Computer Languages: Java (w/ the Spring & Spring Boot frameworks), HTML, CSS, XML, Git, SQL, JDBC, Apache Derby DB and SQLite

Software Platforms: IntelliJ, Android SDK, including Room ORM, Eclipse, Jshell, Postman, Photoshop, Illustrator, Microsoft Office, MacOS, iOS, Chrome OS, Safari OS

Other: Version Control, Object Oriented Programming, Agile Methodologies, Material Design

RECENT EXPERIENCE

DeepDive Java & Mobile Developer Intern

2019

Certificate 480 Hours of Java Programming & Android App Development

Manager 2012 - 2018

Albuquerque, NM

Deacon Property Services

- Supervised and coordinated contractors doing commercial and residential rebuild projects
- Supervised and trained the maintenance and inspection staff.

Regional Director 1999 - 2012

Seattle, WA

Schiller Institute

- Analyzed team performance on a weekly basis through review of income generated and material distributed.
- Trained worked force in sales and community engagement

EDUCATION

CS courses at UNM: Beginning & Intermediate Java Linear Algebra Discrete Mathematics	2015 - 2016
Completed many PHP, Illustrator, Wordpress, website building courses at Lynda.com	2013 - 2015
Created Website from scratch for Deacon Property Services	2013
BA Philosophy/ Film Studies University of Florida	1991
OTHER	
Android Developers Meetup	2019 - Current